Guide to the Peter H.L. and Edith Chang Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IX: Photographs
  - Negatives: 1964-1965, 1973-1974, undated (Box 82)
  - Negatives: 1976-1980 (Box 83)
  - Negatives: 1981-1990 (Box 84)
  - Slides: 1943-1949, 1962-1968 (Box 85)
  - Slides: 1941-1942, 1961-1968 (Box 86)
  - Slides: 1961-1966 (Box 87)
  - 1960s-1990s, undated (Box 90)
  - Albums (4): 1967-1968 (Box 93)
  - 1990 (Box 94)
  - Two separate mounted photos of Chang, Peter H. L. and Edith Chang [n.p., n.d.] (Box 14-L-1)
  - Two separate of H. L. Chang and of H. L. Chang and Edith Chang together in Hawaii. [n. p.: 1992] (Box 14-L-1)
- Series X: Personal Effects
  - Miscellaneous (unidentified) documents and manuscripts, (2 notebooks; lists; loose pages; printed items) (Box 46)
  - Makeup Kit (Box 88)
  - Hair cutting Kit (Box 89)
  - Seals (Box 91)
  - Bibles (2) (Box 92)